Time.
forever.
then. to.
then. what?
Shall we kiss?
kiss what?
I can't even be friends with you.
I'm not even friends with you anymore, I'm just friends.
How does your friend change when you report it?
Is your friend coming back?
Shall we kiss?
You said so.
I'm excited, I'm excited
Uh.
Bug car you.
No, why am I so excited?
Did you run away? No, suddenly tall.
Let's do it. But just stay there.
How can I kiss a country I don't even like?
You don’t know yet whether you like it or not. kiss
You don't have to try to know. I did it but I didn't
If you like it.
Is this your first kiss? What?
I'm going to kiss the person I like
So? Preferred
If your brother asks you to kiss him, can you do it?
Seon-ho oppa likes you.
If Seon-ho says he likes you, kiss him
I will do it.
Why do you think it's a portal?
Can you give me some advice? That is.
Then, in my imagination for the rest of my life
Because I only had one-sided love. It actually happens in reality
You don’t think you can handle those feelings, right?
I'm just comfortable with unrequited love until I die
Who is me?
What do you like?
Because I've never thought about it.
Is that why you can't receive the heart I left behind?
to.
I'm really screwed.
Even though we're no longer friends, should we still be friends?
I.
doesn't exist?
No, I didn't do it, then I will do it
It was obvious. No, never then
Tell me quickly what it is.
at last.
I want to try it, so
Ah. so so
So, tell me quickly, did you run away?
What? I sulked.
If Legend wants to kiss me, I
It's just so tight, I can't
You should have pretended to win, you fool, I don’t like it.
How should your heart flow now?
It's important that you live with such a handsome boy.
Yoyo. There is no need for the government to clash
You have to check your heart first whether you want to do it or not.
You have to kiss to confirm your feelings. That heart
You have to check first so you don't die without being able to kiss.
No, they say you have to check your feelings first before you can kiss.
No, no, no. That's right, what to see
I think so. What should I do?
It's all like this, you just make up your mind every day
Check it out.
Who are you? Oh my, yesterday
Since you came from Germany briefly, dinner is coming next week.
Meokjae is annoying. again
Say what you like. I waited so long.
If you wait, who will wait?
What was the shortcut key for this?
Oh, of course, thank you, Bu Seon-ho.
There are no stone powder cookie princesses either.
I don't even have a date or a face-to-face meeting, but it's the same
It must be awkward because of the team.
We're lucky, it'll be less awkward.
Right.
Ah, so it went well.
It will be less awkward with me.
Yes, the time is after the Sunday meeting.
Okay, I'll make a reservation. Okay, okay.
It's really neat, yeah. Okay,
Okay.
It finally feels a little more natural now, huh?
okay? What
Okay, okay?
Uh huh?
I want to kiss, I want to kiss, kiss
Do you want to try?
Are report cards coming out this week?
uh. uh.
Don't spread the word that it's over now, just study a little more.
Soon, on the day of the exam, my brother
I just studied all night, okay?
Yoona, please close the refrigerator door.
yes.
What is our concept this week? concept
Recommended. Um, me too during the triangle.
haunted house.
Is there a concept you want to try?
Hey, why was it rejected and the petition was also rejected?
Wow, what do you have after being rejected for a kiss?
Embarrassed Rabbit You will be embarrassed in an inappropriate way, right?
Yes, fellow student, please be honest. you
I really wanted to kiss you when I was learning.
After finding out what you like and what you are like,
Actually, it's just a kiss
You must have wanted it. That black heart was discovered
That's why it's embarrassing, right?
That's me.
Now god. Let's not report it.
Oh, I'm so embarrassed that I can't even look at that pot-bellied face.
Should I just apologize and say I was wrong?
Let's change the strategy, now we're pulling
Stop now.
Build when using this?
Just pretend like nothing happened.
Nothing really happened.
Avoiding it is even weirder.
Babble Pie.
hello. uh.
Hi is the structure? Hello,
Did you do well on the test? Well
I don't know. Coincidentally, exams are over and we have a company dinner.
How about next time? Today
Our date?
You two get along really well
I think so. But like that
No, why are you waiting?
hurry. That July
Why are you taking off your clothes because you don't like it? splash
I prepared hard because I hated it. brown talk
Where are you? Is there a pink rabbit whose body has been plucked?
Then let's ask those people. who is more
I've been trying this since yesterday to see if it suits me well.
Don't think of me as a spark for a childish argument.
Because I just don't want to get involved even for a second.
This is my seat.
hello.
Oh, you two are a couple. Who is the couple?
It's amazing, it's really true.
Why are you doing this? compliment
I'm going to the bathroom
Uh.
uh.
If you cover your face like that, you can see ahead.
It's cute today.
I look at it.
hello? No, are you here?
They look like a couple.
The two of us can do any coffee pose. Ah,
That looks so cute. Oh yeah.
But why doesn't the earrings come? Ah that
The kid probably won't come out today. what
Something happened and it turned into a caterpillar again.
But what?
This video is not red.
What is this? Is this red?
That's right.
Why on earth is this happening?
The name is crazy.
Hey you crazy idiot, you really do that on the subway
Is it burnt? It's red after all
I envy your guts. Really I am that
Not even if you only have guts.
hi.
Is it a concept?
Harlequin, icon of vengeance.
Hey, today's dress code is animals.
What about Korean? You have to listen to it until the end
That's okay? In the trap for Harlequin
It represented a single bird that was caught.
more. temperature.
Is there one?Reference.
Parts without blood or tears make a lot of money.
What are you talking about, kid? Where are you looking at this?
Huh?
crow.
Prepare the same thing.
What are you full?
ah. jeon.
king.
By any chance?
uh.
Shall we begin?
Let’s start with our cutie’s belly.
Does it look too good?
The title is One Hurt Bird. What happened earlier?
Do you keep getting hurt? Hey, you're just an asshole.
If you don't do it right, you'll die?
It's by chance.
Let's get started.
Next to the end of Japan.
Japanese luxury business.
Japan and next month?
next person next person
Ah. Stop it
How many did you do? Like this
I haven't even done a hundred, but I got this right
Is it Hansan University?
Look at this ugly thing.
Did your child turn around? Why should I hit you?
I will take revenge.
I'll do it next time you see it.
Start in Japan.
uh. They use charcoal.
Yes, I thought it would be fun. wood burning
Originally, my face got buried here and there.
I taste delicious. uh.
That's it.
Like this.
ah.
Both ruling and opposition parties are good. believe it
What are you guys doing?
It happened. What is this? Dongyeong
Let’s go without planes, citizens.
Let's follow along.
I'm jealous.
good night. Now
Everyone, be careful not to fall and follow closely.
Be careful and don't fall.
I saw the first piece of meat today, right? Everyone applaud.
I just have to film a commercial today.
Because you worked hard, this is special
Same z.
Dinosaur
Ah. Once done
Next distribution?
Where are you going?
To poop.
Hey, really, why are you like that today?
These days, your Uber isn't even Uber. Today
I'm only in pain for my stomach. Is it an excess of hormones? Especially today
I don't know where it will go. What are you two doing?
Did you have any work? name nail work
I'm sorry, my sister is not good enough to be like that.
I added him as my younger brother. No, but you siblings
#1 Is it fun? Suddenly there is a lot of friendship
There is none. So, am I going to quit here that day?
Hey, that doesn't happen. Then
Thank goodness.
Try it. I drew up a plan, but why isn’t there anything?
Shouldn’t I wash it? I
I'll bring Bigfoot, yeah.
Ki Jeong-hwa over there?
It's there. last night
The app stays in front of the beacon.
Yes, it's here.
Where is the beacon going?
Today's special guest Bigfoot has an offer to appear.
I refused. Crokin today
That's it. It's hot. Let's have some ice cream.
Let's take a bowl each. Ah, yes,
Then Red has lyrics and an app.
Shall we go together? Then ah
I don't like it, leave it to me.
Bring the app with you.
When speaking of John.
Ah Mr. ah.
Then? I will write it.
Oh, choose something delicious.
I'll be back. I see a skull.
Hey coffee coffee uh
Just looking at that makes it look lovely.
Well, my brother met
It's really, really, really boring
I apologize. Still, Harley Quinn
The makeup was perfect.
What are you doing right?
Hockey Dragon should be a hit
Ka uh. Just another time.
You are so hard
I feel embarrassed somewhere.
after. I was in big trouble.
Is it really not there?
Ah, I can't find it, but it's the ice cream that Hoolegan Lee mentioned.
None.
Watch.
It flowed. Where have you been? on the floor
Did you get scolded for the one thing left? Why couldn't I see it?
If you think it's there, you have to find it. None
If you think about it and look for it, you won’t see it, right?
I thought about this again and found it.
no. You're thinking about something else
Did you find it? Thinking it doesn't exist and looking for it
Same thing.
There's something to calculate.
I'll calculate it and come back.
uh.
Yes, just like at the crosswalk earlier.
Ha, if you look at it again, you can see the real breasts on the shoulders.
Is she your girlfriend, Oliver?
Do you like it? Being my younger sister.
That's not it either. If you are a stalker
Even if you don’t know?
What are you going to do when it's okay?
excuse me.
I'm not a stalker. The condition is that I
No, it's fireworks. Unilaterally before discharge
I'm liking it.
Your payment has been made. Someone asked. Why are you arguing
I'm making a fuss. Do you know the phone? that
You don’t even know what it means. But why do you carelessly
You are talking. How old are you? Ah
What are you talking about all the time? What are you guys
Don't touch my girl carelessly,
You like me, you don't like me, you like me
I like you so much, I'm a stalker, I'm a stalker
I'm Sokoji and I'm scared again.
What are these kids?
Yuan Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Have you ever been like this
There's a lot of useful content, right? oh
If the blood dries on your head, you die.
This is why things don't work out with you.
Yes. Well, I didn't do anything wrong.
It's because of you that I'm having trouble going to class.
Just because of this existence, I am compared and my self-esteem is low.
Since I'm falling, don't like me.
Because I don’t like you either.
uh.
And I'm ugly
Ah.
ah.
uh.
How about having a company dinner today for the first time in a while?
Green In One and I had something to do.
What are you two?Date no.
Assignment: I have to go early today too.
I think it will work. The exam is over
Why then let’s just go today?
Well, see you next time.
I'll go first. Try it out and do well.
No. It's a task.
Why did I get stoned so much?
Did you do that? Ah, ah yes.
Just like everyone else, you are now in big trouble. Oh hey
Since the cow broke the coffee, I have to take responsibility now.
Is your number okay?
Now it’s nice to see it in my dreams too.
sorry. Teacher, hit me instead.
I said it's okay. Oh, I'll take responsibility for everything.
Oh, you just lower your nose too
If you sit down, I will perform the surgery.
Really? I'm losing my mind right now.
huh. Then take responsibility for my grades first?
Where did we decide to go from here?
uh.
uh. eww.
Because I'm just leaving. me too
Or are you saying that if the roots are going to produce something, they're going to need sound?
Oh, is this correct?
Now I have to read the magazine
Ah.
three.
Ah, I was actually worried. today's assignment
Will we become awkward again while practicing?
I'm curious about what to write in the report? Honestly
I'm going to write it. The only feeling I have today is day 1
My date, Koo Seon-ho, is nice and when we're together,
It's fun and puts people at ease. And goodbye
He is very good at keeping his word.
Anyway, I actually didn't believe you.
Did you think it would continue to be uncomfortable?
however.
why?
Why are you looking at me like that again? It’s strange again
I tried to shout, but let's go, let's go, let's go, you are so serious
Do you feel anxious every time you call my name? I'm afraid it will develop rapidly again
Something nicer, fun and comfortable to be with? yesterday today
It's not work, so don't make anything special about it. It was rushed.
I know I shouldn't force it
I know. Because it's you
Hey, how much am I because of you?
what? Are you going after this semester?
Was I a little anxious?
however.
This place opened a while ago, really.
It's delicious. What do you like?
I really like what you like. Your reservation has been confirmed. If you receive guidance
It works. Come on
Come, have you made a reservation? My name is Kim Na-young,
Nayoung Kim.
Hyuna, here.
All right. Why do I feel like this, I'm starving to death
I knew it.
Mom, you like 5-day pasta, right?
Mom, why have you become so pretty? Ah
Mom.
boa. BL Mail,
mail.
Sorry.
I'm singing a song that I miss you no matter how much I prepare
Did you call him and bring him? Oh, this is Habit.
February, is your sister pretty?
uh.
Should we order steak too?
How is the atmosphere here?
I think it's good. I'm sorry
Listen. I'm weak so just do a little bit
I wish I could eat it wrong. Hurry up on the bridge
Go. Say something like it hurts a lot.
Mom will call me and catch me again.
Just eat something more delicious.
Sorry for the protests. Levi.
A company. what? Any other thoughts?
Why are you being so boring today?
Strangely, it's not fun.
Where are you? I said I would go.
Shouldn't you do it? A smooth face
Are you trusting or criticizing me? I fed him and played with him and I
It’s okay, I look like your friend. Oh, I’m sorry.
Sorry, I suddenly became middle-aged.
It's manners.
Is it over with you? I got dumped.
Pretending to be okay, pretending like nothing is wrong.
Aren’t you comfortable with a poker face?
Better not get too used to it.
Usually, you forget your own face first.
They sold this over there. I sold it all over there.
It's done. well
Go. ah.
If you throw away food, you will be punished. Do you eat it?
Are you sure you're not good?
I'm sorry I'm not good-looking.
I'm ugly. Ah,
That's just what I said.
you are pretty in the world
Number 1: Are you saying you’re pretty?
uh.
green pig alcohol on a moonlit night
intake.
Yes, are you there today?
yes.
ah.
hey.
madam. ah.
What's going on?
okay. I also ate and asked to hear the answer.
No. instead?
Let me answer your question, right?
Look at me, why am I like this?
Was I born unnecessarily handsome?
Green pig, just like you and me
Born in the womb?
Are my mom and dad different?
uh.
yes.
Is it still too far to search? Wow
Is this your new score?
It's serious, but what is this?
Same thing with having to go to the military.
Like you? Ha.
afternoon. Wow
The number of bags has really increased.
It's birth. Ah. No, then
Should we take a short break? Then you didn't see it
People watch and take a break for ten minutes, then five minutes.
We will proceed like that.
What did you do before memorizing it?
This is a bit. What is it? I
You didn't do that at all, right?
hey. Did you see this picture well?
ah. I'm crazy about this picture
Did you see it? Is it brown or pink again?
Of course I drew it well, because I did it. But
I didn't. uh.
Don't do cafe cars, really?
I didn't want to do that because I was bad at contacting them. Why?
hey.
I'm sorry for contacting you because I'm ugly, huh?
What is it? Gagcon.
Is it his fault? What's wrong
If so? Unnecessarily handsome
That's all. Ah
That way.
yes.
however. Are you hiding again?
I don't know?
There's a bit of distance between you and me these days.
I think so. what?
first.
prince.
S I've done it all
All iCash for you
Your boyfriend is your boyfriend. No.
I guess that’s not true, how come
Just wait like this for a moment. You look handsome um
Better than a complete legend
Why dubbing? If you're handsome
Send it. It is essential.
Would you stop looking at it?
Which of these is number one?
Are you ugly? Hey, what and what?
Shall I hit you?
Hey, you don't know how to become ugly
You know? Oh, is this really your daughter? Leave it alone
Why don't you know? Oh, you don't know? variable
Don't ignore it. I am also popular with my sisters.
Oh, that’s right, you were yesterday, brother and sister.
Did you meet well? Kim Kyung-geol wasn't able to do it.
Anyway, who will meet each other seriously?
I can't. I'm currently watching ICP, but I don't even watch it anymore.
Grandma, hurry up and don’t disturb me.
Gift transfer yang um.
Are you foolish? I'll be your friend
That's why my grandmother chose it for me.
Isn't it pretty?
I heard it's amazing, so what's tomorrow?
Do I have to report it? What do you like?
I've seen it all, I've only heard that word
I'm just pretending to be friendly. My mom says
My mom said she was really unlucky with her hands.
That's right, that's right?
oh. Mom,
I really am.
Ah, this is basic these days, right?
I hear people say I can't take care of myself
I just hate that. i am me
How can you help kids if you can't come together yourself?
Can you take care of it? Do we do it like this?
That's right, Odoran Maran, born with us.
It's different, he was really famous in his old days.
What kind of work was it from Ballerina?
No, Giselle did a lot, right?
What would you do if you were successful in your old days? for now
I will believe it. only two sons
She's a woman who doesn't have one, but her son at Seoul National University
I left my gifted son behind.
The kid is so cute. Such a son
I feel sad for the woman who doesn't have one. Ah
Sorry sorry.
and. Just a little bit
Sleep with a cooler feeling
Feeling okay go look seagull seagull
Should I do it? Just like this.
Why didn’t you just leave?
So don’t you like me, me too
Because you won't like it.
It's over, I'm leaving. It's not working. It's too small.
Dude, why are you dragging me around like you want again? and
I need to buy a business quickly, you are the boss
Can't you hear me when I talk now?
this?
No, not this, no.
Dad, it's not me.
Why is that light broken?
Sorry, sorry, I didn't want to answer the phone.
I didn't do it, I suddenly got a phone call and I was shaking.
No, I was surprised. that
Anyway, why did you call me?
You know what?
Do you have any good news? I'll be there today
It's ugly. Do you want to meet?
ah.
what?
I'm right, I'm ugly.
Sorry. uh.
What what yesterday?
Also, are you a beggar?
And it's not wrong either.
ah. hey.
You said it before, right?
There are days when I feel like a ten-won coin
There is. Was yesterday that kind of day?
Is it because my heart isn't right?
Are you mad at me?
sorry.
Me then. Even if you keep liking me
Is it okay? You're angry
I kept telling you not to like me. no.
That's what I said too, that's important right now
It's not true, right? It's important. you
If I keep liking you even though I don't like it, that's a stalker.
There is also a stalk law. Even if I still like you
Is it okay? I don’t know, do whatever you want.
Don't ask such things.
home. Everyone will like me now
Huh? No.
I like that you have low self-esteem because of me.
I told him not to, but he said that was wrong, so again
It's the starting point, I can like you too, you too
It's okay to like me.
What is it? That strangely
I feel persuaded. Still not sure?
Rom.
Do you want to try U-Kiss again?
It's too cold.
Sparsely?
Ah, first of all, you're good, you're such a bad player, huh?
Beverages, Seoul National University.
There is, I don’t need it.
Drink?
uh
Huh?
Really, what is Baekgu there, heavy rain?
What are you doing?
Did you come alone?
Did you come for a kiss? Let's go see flowers together
Then did the student go to see it?
I also come here with my friends
I came to see it. he is now
I've heard of drinks. I'm cool
It's the third semester of this grade.
area.
Lee Jeong-i, Ki-jeong-ui.
Grandma, this is a gift from me.
gift.
however.
Grandma, you are so pretty
It looks pretty.
Because it has a name, it reminds me of my childhood
When I was young?
I also used to make and use it.
I'm done.
For some reason, it feels like he died as a child.
Without even realizing it.
I'm sorry, I wasn't very good at drawing it, right?
You must have been innocent and pretty, but no.
I did it again.
Thank you so much, teacher.
A picture I drew on my own.
I opened my grandmother’s memory box.
We are. treasure in it
Same stories. It's been a while.
I listened to it for a while.
Grandma, be proud of yourself.
Warm like a spring breeze.
In her voice.
Hey, you climbed too. Well, if you compare the loss, it also went up.
No. Are you finally getting it from the lady for a painting meeting?
I'm going to tell you today, at this level, even my mom will approve.
I think I'm finally ending my shameful double life.
I appeal to you. yes.
Oppa, you can do well too
You know. Now my mom
All this time, for no reason
Yeah, right now
tutoring.
See you yet.
mom. Because my grades went up
Please grant me one wish. Wade
Shall we go to the department store? no.
There's a meeting I want to attend. A meeting?
Isn’t this a book club essay?
It's a painting group?
What? What am I doing now?
Are you talking? What kind of meeting, no, suddenly
What picture am I drawing?
In the future, are you going to be with kids you've been friends with since childhood?
No, it's not like that, it's a meeting like that.
It doesn't matter if you draw, just get together with people who like drawing
So what can a kid who doesn’t even know how to draw do?
Isn't this a painting club where the kids get together and play around?
It looks so pathetic. It looks like that.
There is even a law that says only people can do it.
That's the law of the world, just do what you're good at
Even if you give it to me, it's hard to survive, please dad
Look. I can't even come home because I'm so busy making money.
Just working all night. Stop talking nonsense.
Wooyeonah. Everyone else is studying
You draw useless pictures like that.
Do you want to waste time? Studying is the only thing I can do
If you want to chase after heels, they'll give it to you. Where are you when you don't have enough?
Are you saying such strange things?
Don’t be empty and study.
Don't say that it's useless.
What? Mom likes it
Don't ignore it like that just because it's not happening. no
Who ignored whom?
You ignored me. Mom every day
You look down on me, compare me, and ignore me.
Mom, aren’t you the kind of person who can be treated so carelessly?
It's like a trash can that I can step on.
No, so don't ignore it. and.
And oh, the kimchi refrigerator in my room.
Clean it up.
eww.
uh. I'm so angry I can't hold back my tears
There wasn't.
several.
It won't come out.
Hoya. quickly
Open the door mom, 123 is real
Ah.
It's not because I couldn't get permission to hold a croquis gathering.
That my mother is that kind of person.
I was so angry. I was sad.
Are you calling now?
What is it? Is it strange?
Oh, I saw how ugly I was.
What? I’m full.
It won't hurt for a day or two.
Still, when I called, my voice was heard.
uh. Hang up, whatever.
Don't call me. That?
no.
Is something strange?
yes.
You're not leaving now, are you?
Why are you leaving home, stupid? Going to school?
What?
Is it a secret from your mom?
Dojo Dawson. It's our country
You didn't do it. So
Do you have to come after school?
of course?
uh.
There is po.
Can I use it in multiple cases?
Are you running into your mom? Go
All you have to do is wait.
By skype.
Did you move?
Oh, I forgot.
Why are you here? I'm going to school now.
It hasn't happened yet, so why are you here?
Are aliens real? Why are you contacting me?
Why aren't you answering my phone call?
Are you nervous and won’t accept it?
Why is your face like this? Who hit you?
Who out there is right?
also. Did you cry?
No, I posted a lot of Mr. Wa’s clothes.
Hey, who are you? Just tell me. I
I will come and take away your tears.
uh.
Why are you smiling? Do you think I can't do it?
Who talks to my mom like that?
You're the only one there, really?
uh. you my mom
Can’t I upload it? My mom
How strong is it?Mom
I'm scared.
Is it bad to get water?
uh.
I really don't know what to say
Don't you know? Stay still
Just by looking at it, you accidentally touch it
To taste.
sounds easy
Hold on tightly
It's there, it's precious.
Here for a long time
Please wait, I'm sorry
'Cause it's me and the bulldog
This is the angle this time
Won with this return,
Whatever we are, I
I will take responsibility. you never let me
Sorry, but don't ever think about my charm.
Don't ever look at me anew. Affiliation like this
Did you receive it this well? There's a child on your lips
Do you have any help? Kilo as a friend
I don't even think about it. I probably also sent the socks I had.
Why is he doing something he doesn't do before?
A person like you has done this until now too.
I never said it never happened, my ex
This is my boyfriend.
Should you have seen our Namdong caterpillar?
Hey this time? If you keep doing this, I'll be very upset.
Explode? The caterpillar shell enters middle school
It's a gift. Dad? Seoul Dad too
Why do I treat pink like a blanket to a man?
hey. If I originally put it on, it would be that child.
Will I die?